<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"> <id>/</id><title>Reset your code</title><subtitle>My notes and stories.</subtitle> <updated>2024-04-12T08:57:03+00:00</updated> <author> <name>Piotr Stapp</name> <uri>/</uri> </author><link rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" href="/feed.xml"/><link rel="alternate" type="text/html" hreflang="en" href="/"/> <generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.2.2">Jekyll</generator> <rights> © 2024 Piotr Stapp </rights> <icon>/assets/img/favicons/favicon.ico</icon> <logo>/assets/img/favicons/favicon-96x96.png</logo> <entry><title>Exploring Azure Container Apps (ACA) and the Missing YAML Functionality</title><link href="/ACA-missing-yaml/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Exploring Azure Container Apps (ACA) and the Missing YAML Functionality" /><published>2024-04-09T08:30:12+00:00</published> <updated>2024-04-12T08:56:31+00:00</updated> <id>/ACA-missing-yaml/</id> <content src="/ACA-missing-yaml/" /> <author> <name>Piotr Stapp</name> </author> <summary> Introduction Have you ventured into the world of Azure Container Apps (ACA)? If not, let’s dive in! I recently spent some time exploring ACA, and while it offers several benefits, there’s one crucial feature that’s conspicuously absent: the ability to use YAML configurations from Kubernetes (K8s). In this post, I’ll discuss ACA, its advantages, and why the inclusion of YAML support would be a g... </summary> </entry> <entry><title>Quo Vadis, Open-source?</title><link href="/quo-vadis-open-source/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Quo Vadis, Open-source?" /><published>2024-04-09T08:30:12+00:00</published> <updated>2024-04-09T08:30:12+00:00</updated> <id>/quo-vadis-open-source/</id> <content src="/quo-vadis-open-source/" /> <author> <name>Piotr Stapp</name> </author> <summary> Reflecting on the past year, I’ve become increasingly convinced that the open-source model faces challenges from various angles. Here are my favorite moments from last months: 👉 Moq - the dotnet open source library for mocking The owner added a SponsorLink that was sending a hash of developer email to a cloud service. Why? Because the owner wanted to test how they could get funds for their wor... </summary> </entry> <entry><title>6 steps to pimp my terminal</title><link href="/geting-secrets-from-github-actions/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="6 steps to pimp my terminal" /><published>2023-01-18T08:30:12+00:00</published> <updated>2023-01-18T08:03:47+00:00</updated> <id>/geting-secrets-from-github-actions/</id> <content src="/geting-secrets-from-github-actions/" /> <author> <name>Piotr Stapp</name> </author> <summary> How to get secrets from GitHub Actions Working with secrets can be hard. Especially when you forget their values, and you would like to retrieve them. In my case I didn’t store Azure service principal for test environment anywhere. Moreover I wanted to move them from project level into organization level. Unfortunately reading them from GitHub is not possible, but the actions have them. What ... </summary> </entry> <entry><title>6 steps to pimp my terminal</title><link href="/few-steps-to-pimp-my-terminal/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="6 steps to pimp my terminal" /><published>2021-06-02T09:15:12+00:00</published> <updated>2022-07-23T12:51:26+00:00</updated> <id>/few-steps-to-pimp-my-terminal/</id> <content src="/few-steps-to-pimp-my-terminal/" /> <author> <name>Piotr Stapp</name> </author> <summary> Tools My current setup is mixed of tools from following list: oh-my-posh + powerlevel10k_rainbow (with mods) theme + custom font posh-git Set-PSReadlineKeyHandler for “bash style” search + autocomplete PSKubectlCompletion with PSKubeContext for kubernetes Register-ArgumentCompleter for dotnet MagicTooltips which is responsible for displaying tooltips for kubectl and az If you j... </summary> </entry> <entry><title>Make PowerShell with k8s great again</title><link href="/pskube-context/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Make PowerShell with k8s great again" /><published>2021-05-31T13:38:51+00:00</published> <updated>2021-05-31T13:38:51+00:00</updated> <id>/pskube-context/</id> <content src="/pskube-context/" /> <author> <name>Piotr Stapp</name> </author> <summary> So, like me, you’re using Windows. WSL isn’t always reliable (e.g. VPN problems), yet you’re working with Kubernetes and require autocomplete tools. I’m the same way :) Kubectl autocomplete With bash or zsh, having autocomplete is straightforward. Almost only one command is required to complete the task: source &amp;lt;(kubectl completion bash) However, this will obviously not work in PowerShel... </summary> </entry> </feed>
